Is there seriously no one?
If anyone...
has even the slightest
recollection of him at all...
It's all right. That's enough, Subaru.
This is Julius.
Julius Juukulius.
I think you've all figured this out,
but he's one of Gluttony's victims
that's been left nameless.
But he retains his consciousness.
All of Gluttony's victims until now
either had their memories consumed
and ended up like Lady Crusch
or had both their names and their
memories consumed, like Rem.
But Julius only had his name consumed.
You mean he's an exception?
Everyone else has forgotten
him, but he remembers himself?
He wears the uniform of a knight.
I'm sure he was an acquaintance
of myself and Ferris,
or perhaps even closer than that.
At the very least,
I thought of you as friends.
Damn it!
Just two friends?
I don't think that's all there is to it.
Lady Anastasia...
I've got a suggestion for all of ya.
May I?
There are people in this city
who were either transformed by Lust
or left nameless by Gluttony.
We may have captured the Sin Archbishops,
but I doubt they're gonna just come
out and tell us how to fix 'em.
So we're stuck.
Did you have to bring that up right now?!
In which case...
we just gotta ask someone
else who probably knows.
Someone else who probably knows?
Someone really smart?
That's right.
And there's someone really smart
here in this country, ain't there?
Quit being vague! Just tell us who it is!
You don't mean...
Shaula the Sage.
Shaula?
Yep.
One of the three great
heroes of Lugunica...
Shaula the Sage.
Long ago, in the Dragonfriend
Kingdom of Lugunica,
there was a group of heroes
who accomplished great deeds.
The Sword Saint, the Dragon
Lord, and the Sage,
known collectively as
the three great heroes.
Right?
Yep.
The keeper of knowledge who foresees
everything that will ever be.
In the Auguria Dunes at the
far eastern edge of Lugunica
stands the Pleiades Watchtower,
built to guard the sealed Witch of Envy.
The legendary sage who
lives in seclusion there
just might have the answers
we're lookin' for.
Frankly, I'm still against this.
I mean, that's the place even you
weren't able to get to, right?
Two years ago, when the
royal family fell ill,
I set out for the Pleiades
Watchtower in search of a cure
by order of the council.
But... I never made it there.
No matter how far I traveled, the tower
in the distance never drew closer.
It must have been some sort of barrier,
and I was unable to cross it.
The Auguria Dunes are famous for
being a giant den of mabeasts, right?
Should Mister Natsuki and the others
really be going there on their own?
All we can do is have faith.
I have a duty to escort Lady
Felt and that Sin Archbishop.
Besides...
there are still people
in this city who need us.
A place Reinhard failed to get into, huh?
When I just hear that part,
this all seems pretty hopeless.
Subaru, you're getting a
scary look on your face.
If you get so lost in thought that
you neglect our physical contact,
then Betty's cuteness will
go to waste, I suppose.
Oh, sorry!
Wait, you're right!
I only zoned out for a minute,
and look how uggy you've gotten!
I have not! Argh!
Beatrice.
Isn't it just about your bedtime?
Would you like to sleep with me tonight?
I'll do that, I suppose.
Staying up all night
is bad for your health.
Natsuki, you're still up?
Yeah.
Even on a safe road, someone
should keep watch, right?
Yeah, we just don't have
enough people, do we?
Sure wish Ricardo would've come with us...
But with his arm like that...
How about you tell the truth already?
Huh? Where's this comin' from?
What are ya—
You're a lousy actor. Just drop it.
You're not Lady Anastasia.
Quit having your way with
her face and voice.
How strange.
How did you know I wasn't Ana?
Something's seemed off this whole
time, but I know for sure now.
Lady Anastasia is a realist,
but she'd never talk so
coldly about a close friend
with an injury that'll change his life.
It's a bit embarrassing when I
keep getting outed left and right.
Left and right? I'm not the only one?
Priscilla Barielle.
The one who called me a vixen.
She is a scary one.
Who are you?
What are you trying to—
Echidna.
What?
My name is Echidna.
As for what I am... well, I'm what
they call an artificial spirit.
Frankly, it's not surprising that
you'd think I took over Ana's body.
That's why I was hesitant
to tell you the truth.
What kind of terrible joke is this?
You're... Echidna?
In Lady Anastasia's form?
Wait, were you behind everything
that just happened in Priestella?!
Would you just calm down?
I think there's a huge
misunderstanding here...
You expect me to calm
down, you vile witch?!
What have you done with Lady Anastasia?!
I wish you'd stop treating me like
the mastermind of some evil scheme.
I have no intention of harming Ana.
I've been with her for over ten years.
What the hell are you...
Wait, over ten years?
Let me clear up
the misunderstanding first.
I'm not the Echidna you're thinking of.
Other than the fact that
I'm an artificial spirit
and the fact that my name is Echidna,
I know nothing about myself.
You're an artificial spirit?
Like Beako?
Strictly speaking, this fox muffler
Ana always wears is my real body.
So I've been watching all
of you for a long time.
Are you telling me this now
because you're finally fully prepared
to take over her body, Foxidna?
Foxidna?
I'm not sure I really like that name...
I have no intention of
taking over Ana's body.
The current situation is
not what I wanted.
If it's not what you wanted,
why don't you go back into
that fox muffler already?
I would love to do just that...
but I no longer can.
Explain.
What state is Lady Anastasia's
body in right now?
To be blunt...
I'm using Ana's od as a medium
to overwrite her consciousness
with my own.
Her consciousness is sleeping
at the depths of her od,
and I have full control over her body.
I can even use magic with her gate,
even though it's defective.
Her gate is defective?
Then won't using magic now
put strain on her body?!
I'm only doing something
that chips away at her life
because her life was in
danger to begin with.
I have, of course, talked with Ana
about this and earned her consent.
So this isn't the first time
you've borrowed her body?
There were a few other occasions,
but none where I became unable to return.
So I'm at a loss right now myself.
You see, I love Ana.
I don't know if I'm right about
this since I lack the experience,
but I feel as if she's something
very close to family.
I just want her to be as healthy—
and above all, as happy—as possible.
So the real reason you
want to see the Sage is...
I only want to know how
to give Ana her body back.
I'll use you and your companions
for that if I must.
Can you be certain the Sage knows
how to get you back to normal?
I'm not.
But if this Sage sees all
and knows all, as they say,
there's a chance.
I will make the choice that
offers the highest probability of success.
No more or less.
I can't say I accept this,
but I understand.
You have a goal and know
what you need to do,
and it doesn't interfere with our goal.
Indeed. We both have things
we wish to ask the Sage.
Okay, got it.
Just don't mention borrowing
Lady Anastasia's body to Julius...
or to anyone else.
That's fine, but I'm surprised
you won't be telling them.
The timing sucks as it is.
I just don't want to make
unnecessary waves right now.
I see.
There's someone else you want to ask
the Sage how to help, after all, yes?
Well...
We'll stop by Margrave
Mathers' mansion on the way.
I'm sure you'll also want to
prepare to cross the dunes,
but that's where your sleeping beauty is.
You intend to take her with you, correct?
That ain't a bad thing, if ya ask me.
We'll still save all of 'em.
It just comes down to
who's gonna be first.
I don't think anyone would blame
ya for gettin' that as a perk.
Rem...
Your letter informed me of the situation.
So, you minimized casualties in the
battle against Sin Archbishops?
I'm relieved to know that
Garf was of use, as well.
Master Otto also seems to be safe—
Ugh!
Mister Otto is always so reckless!
And after we were able to
send such good news, too!
Yeah, I hear the meeting with
all the fakes went well.
You'll have to tell us all about it later.
Yeah! I mean... yes!
Aw, what a sinful man you are, Natsuki.
Subaru, I can see why they
call you the Little Girl User.
Just so you know, Petra isn't
a "little" girl anymore!
And if I do use any little
girls, it's only Beako!
The outcome in Priestella wasn't
just thanks to Garfiel and Otto.
Everyone in the city worked
hard to achieve it.
But...
You're heading for the Sage's tower to
save the victims of Gluttony and Lust.
A dangerous path, indeed.
Is there even any chance of success?
I'm sure this is a cause of great
concern to you, Margrave Mathers.
But there are still many in Priestella
whose bodies and minds are damaged
thanks to the Witch Cult's evil deeds.
What an elegant way of putting it.
Since I have not
recognized you, I assume...
you are one of them yourself?
We're talking about where
things stand here.
We stopped by the mansion
for Rem and one other thing.
The one currently in the
mansion's prison, yes?
My, my. What an unusual visitor.
Yeah. I have important
business with you, Meili.
The Auguria Dunes?
Yes, I've been there to
replenish my mabeasts before.
They really are all over
the place, you know.
Yes! That's what I want to know!
I want to learn from the experience
of someone who's been there!
There's a huge difference between
info that's backed by experience
and info that isn't, you know?
And it's very reassuring for
someone without experience!
If there's something you want
me to do, just spit it out.
Right.
If we have a mabeast user like you with us,
we might make it
through the dunes unscathed.
So would you come with us—
Fine.
I realize you don't want
to go outside, of course.
But if you could... just...
I said I'm willing to go with you.
What? You are?
I'll do whatever you want
me to do about the mabeasts.
I can keep them away, tame them,
make them kill each other, or
even make them eat the Sage.
Don't do those last two!
Also, I thought you were
refusing to leave the mansion.
I'm afraid of Mom finding me,
but I don't want to be
locked up in here forever.
This isn't going to be
some fun little jaunt.
It'll be my first walk in a long time.
Maybe it's better if it
offers some excitement.
All right! We'll be counting on you!
Don't get all friendly with me.
I'm not like Beatrice and Petra, you know.
What's up, Julius?
I was just thinking.
About being forgotten...
and forgetting.
Which is more painful, I wonder?
How am I supposed to know?
Screw this! No getting all sentimental!
Forgetting and being forgotten
can both kiss my ass!
Don't try to rank how painful things are!
Subaru...
And quit looking so discouraged!
Did you forget, Julius?
Wait, I mean, don't forget, Julius!
My eyes know just how strong you are!
My humiliation knows it!
No matter who else may forget!
Huh?
Nothing. You truly are a remarkable man.
Just realizing that all over again.
I see. You're right.
It's not as if I've been left
behind by everything and everyone.
I wouldn't say you were left behind.
More like you're three lengths ahead.
Is three enough to cover it?
I oughta pound you!
The pair Beako and I make is
nothing like it was before!
Ram.
I was preparing for our departure.
I changed her clothes and wiped her down.
You're getting a lewd look
on your face. Pervert.
I kept quiet because I didn't know
what to say, and that's what I get?
You might die this time.
Why are you doing this?
I think... I just want to be the first
thing she sees when she wakes up.
Removing all emotions from it,
I know it doesn't matter who wakes her up.
But...
when emotions come into play,
I want to be the one to save her.
I want to save her with all that I am.
You're so dumb.
Sorry it took me so long to see you.
I had to take care of a
bunch of other stuff...
Sorry. That's just an excuse.
It might finally get across.
I'm going to get you back, Rem.
That's my promise to you.
The Reason I'm Taking You With Me
I'm sorry I don't have anything prepared
when you came all the way here.
Oh, uh, sorry for
droppin' by without notice.
We don't wanna put
you through any trouble.
Oh, it's no trouble.
The fact that you make the time
to visit me is so reassuring.
Hey—
My husband...
Garek will be home shortly.
I have faith.
When I was empty and had nothing,
Garek gave me these past ten years.
He even gave me an
adorable son and daughter.
So how could I not have faith in him?
You're really strong.
Yes, of course I am.
I'm a mother of two, after all.
I almost forgot!
There's one thing
I wanted to ask you, too.
Why do you show so much concern
for us, Mister Gorgeous Tiger?
I-I just... can't take my eyes
off ya, for some reason...
You guys are, well...
kinda losin' it, aren't ya?
Oh, how mean!
But it's true, so I can't argue.
Huh? Losing what? Hair?
I lose a bunch of hair
when it gets hot, too!
Are you all right, Mister Gorgeous Tiger?
I'm not sure why,
but you look like a child
who's about to cry.
Mom...
Mom... Mom...
Mom!
I... Mom, I...
Garfiel.
He's Garfiel.
M-Mom...
Mom!
There, there, Garf. You're a good boy.
You've been trying so hard all this time.
I have! I tried so hard, went all-out...
But I got so many things wrong...
But still... But still, everyone...
It's all right. It's all right, Garf.
Your mother is with you now.
Garf, you okee?
Yeah.
Are you all right, Gorgeous Tiger?
A boy crying his eyes out? Unbelievable.
Sorry to make ya worry like that.
I'm gonna go now, so you can relax.
Come visit again anytime.
When you feel like crying,
I'll lend you my shoulder
in your mother's stead.
I'll try to make sure that doesn't happen.
Come on, now, you two. Say goodbye.
See you next time, Gorgeous Tiger!
Come on, Rafiel. You, too.
Ra...fiel?
Yes, Rafiel.
Oh! Did I never introduce you to them?
Their names are...
Fred and Rafiel.
I named them both.
You... named them?
Yes.
When I was thinking of
cute names for babies,
they just came to me.
Fred and... Rafiel...
Frederica... Garfiel...
Well, see ya later, Rafiel and Fred!
I'll come back!
All right, Gorgeous Tiger!
N-Next time, try not to cry, you hear?!
Thanks, Mom.
I'll come visit again!
Gorgeous Tiger Reloaded
Take care of yourselves till then!